Guillaume Jeanneret Sanmiguel

Curriculum Vitae

(+57) 3168668345 ⊠ guillaumejs2403@gmail.com, g.jeanneret@uniandes.edu.co guillaumejs2403.github.io

About me

Summary I am a M.Sc. in Biomedical Engineering from the Universidad de los Andes and a Biomedical Engineer with a minor on Mathematics and Computer Science from the Universidad de los Andes, Bogotá, Colombia, as well. I have knowledge on Machine Learning, specially on Deep Learning, and Applied Mathematics. I have a strong basis on Programming, Mathematics and Machine Learning, specially Deep Learning (DL) using the PyTorch framework. Currently, I work at the Biomedical Computer Vision led by Professor Pablo Arbeláez at the Universidad de los Andes.

Areas of Computer Vision, Deep Learning, Probability, Statistics, Applied Mathematics and Mathe-Interest matical Modelling.

Nationalities Colombian and Swiss

Experience

2018–2020 Research at the Biomedical Computer Vision Group.

2019/01–12 Graduate Research Assistant: Video Analysis

- Research focused on the task One-Shot Video Object Segmentation.
- International Conference paper writing.
- 2018/07-12 Graduate Teaching Assistant: Processing and Image Analysis
 - Laboratory Instructor 80 students in charge.
 - Designing and grading laboratory guides.
 - Final project grading.
- 2018/01–06 Graduate Teaching Assistant: Scientific Programming
 - Laboratory Instructor 65 students in charge.
 - Designing and grading laboratory guides.
 - Final project grading.
- 2017/07–12 Undergraduate Teaching Assistant: Processing and Image Analysis
 - Helping assistant for the lectures.
 - 2016/01- Undergraduate Teaching Assistant: Accompaniment Program 2017/12

- Helping students on first semester courses such as: Differential Calculus, Programming, Physics and Chemistry.
- 2015/07–12 Undergraduate Teaching Assistant: Algorithm and Programming
 - Project grading and assistant on laboratory Java tutorials.

Education

- 2018–2020 **M.Sc. on Biomedical Engineering**, Department of Biomedical Engineering, Universidad de los Andes, Bogotá, Colombia.
- 2013–2018 **B. Biomedical Engineering**, Department of Biomedical Engineering, Universidad de los Andes, Bogotá, Colombia.
 - 2018 **Minor Mathematics and Computer Science**, Department of Biomedical Engineering, Universidad de los Andes, Bogotá, Colombia.
 - 2013 Maturité Suize Degree (Math and Physics emphasis), Helvetia School, Bogotá, Colombia.
 - 2013 High School Degree, Helvetia School, Bogotá, Colombia.

Projects

M.Sc. Thesis MINT: Multi Instance Network, an Efficient Framework for Video Object Segmentation – One-Shot Video Object Segmentation.

MAIN: Multi Attention Instance Network – One-Shot Video Object Segmentation using Deep Learning. Available on arXiv.

Robust Gabor Networks – Robustness properties on architectural layers. Available on arXiv.

MTBI The Dynamics of Math Anxiety as it is Transferred through Peer and Teacher Interactions

– A mathematical model to analyse the transfer of math anxiety

Academic Courses

2018/07–12 Advanced Machine Learning

Summer 2017 MTBI – Research Experience for Undergraduates at the Arizona State University

2017/01-06 Computer Vision

Technical Skills

Programming Python, Matlab

Software LATEX, MS WORD, MS EXCEL, MS POWERPOINT

DL Pytorch

Framework

Languages

Spanish Native

English Fluent

French Fluent